{
    "id": "94ae7dd9cfe24c76be32a4ca8f98a416",
    "title": "Frame Questions",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "..................................... books are these?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Who's",
                "Whose",
                "Whos"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "19f83cfee82745df8257863c7028628e"
        },
        {
            "question": "..................................... do you want?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "What",
                "Whose",
                "Which"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "cfd1fd065f144642bcdc440386af7dbe"
        },
        {
            "question": "........................................... will you stay with?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Whom",
                "What",
                "Which"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "52f765d31a104130864933c90b6ae4f8"
        },
        {
            "question": "With ....................................... are you going?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "who",
                "whom",
                "what"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "c287c235fee44ef898d23da2866cc7b9"
        },
        {
            "question": "....................................... did you go there?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Why",
                "What",
                "Which"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "6f8734a5ebc4435589bcddc9669715df"
        },
        {
            "question": "........................................... is your boy?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Which",
                "What"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "00b561908e524773970b1df8ef2fab1c"
        },
        {
            "question": "......................................... do you come from?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "What",
                "When",
                "Where"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "f7c531a0fe664c97b00776d79c2e17d6"
        },
        {
            "question": "....................................... did you meet him?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "When",
                "Where",
                "How",
                "All of the above"
            ],
            "correct": 3,
            "id": "5371d176739d44e3be7307d9e46f73ae"
        },
        {
            "question": "................................... long is this bridge?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "What",
                "How",
                "Which"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "a9fd22a80f4d494095b9a51f608d5aa0"
        },
        {
            "question": "......................................... old is your father?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "What",
                "How"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "18e8cb1be5584bf2bf498d75cd6ad259"
        },
        {
            "question": "..................................... brothers and sisters do you have?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "How many",
                "How much"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "74c7300431c64f15b99e5607fa285b48"
        },
        {
            "question": "....................................... is your headmaster?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Who",
                "What"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "cae4cfe86ad14b27b71182d66cf8e247"
        },
        {
            "question": "............................................ did you come to this place?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "When",
                "Where",
                "What"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "cf9db904fb914893a398afb9bbd460a3"
        }
    ]
}